Contact

drgillesnp@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/selenagilles (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care

Primary Care

Neurosurgery

Certifications

ANP-BC

Certified Nurse Educator (CNE)
CCRN

Honors-Awards
NBNA Under 40

NLN LEAD Program

Dr Selena Gilles, DNP, ANP-BC, CNEcl, CCRN

Adult Nurse Practitioner

Deer Park, New York

Summary

Experienced Clinical Assistant Professor with a demonstrated history of working in the higher education industry. Skilled in Nursing Education, Medical-Surgical, Primary Care, Patient Education, and Medicine. Strong education professional with a Master's Degree focused in Adult Health Nurse/Nursing from Hunter College.

Experience

NYU Rory Meyers College of Nursing Clinical Assistant Professor August 2014 - Present (5 years 10 months)

ProHEALTH Care
Nurse Practitioner - Neurology
January 2020 - Present (5 months)
Lake Success, New York, United States

Greater New York City - Black Nurses Association 2 years 8 months

Founding Member
October 2017 - Present (2 years 8 months)

Program Committee Chair October 2017 - Present (2 years 8 months)

Kaplan Instructor February 2016 - February 2020 (4 years 1 month)

Garden State Pain Management Nurse Practitioner October 2015 - March 2018 (2 years 6 months) Swedish Institute a College of Health Sciences Instructor January 2014 - August 2014 (8 months)

NYU Rory Meyers College of Nursing Adjunct Clinical Instructor 2010 - May 2014 (4 years)

Weill Cornell Medicine
Nurse Practitioner
May 2011 - February 2014 (2 years 10 months)
Neurosurgery

New York-Presbyterian Hospital RN October 2005 - May 2011 (5 years 8 months) Critical Care

Education

Monmouth University

Doctorate, Nursing Practice

Hunter College
Master's Degree, Adult Health Nurse/Nursing

Long Island University

Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse

Pace University
Pre-Medicine/Pre-Medical Studies